konecranes.com 2016-05-14

# Privacy Policy | Konecranes.com

This Privacy Policy of the Konecranes Group in indented to provide you with general information on the processing of personal data of the Konecranes Group, its employees, partners and affiliates (“Konecranes”) as related to the world wide pages of Konecranes (“Site”).This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains the type of information collected by Konecranes in connection with the Konecranes Site, and how Konecranes processes such information. Konecranes may provide additional or amending privacy information in connection with a particular Konecranes product or service. Such information prevails over this Policy.

Please read this Policy carefully prior to accessing the Site. By using the Site and/or by submitting personal data to Konecranes, you express your agreement to the processing of your personal data in the manner provided in this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, we expect that you will leave this Site and not provide Konecranes with your personal data.

###    
The Data We Collect

Once you register at the Site or have otherwise been assigned a specific identification code to access your account, we may request that you provide certain information such as your name, email address, street address or other information that may be needed to provide the products and services you have requested or to further communicate with you.

###    
The Purposes of Processing

The purpose of processing personal data is to ensure efficient and secure data processing.  Konecranes also strives to continue to develop the Site to ensure the highest quality and a broader scope of services. Additionally, Konecranes may use your personal data to communicate with you. Konecranes may provide additional information relating to our products and/or services or other topics related to the Konecranes Group.

###    
Transfers of Personal Data

Konecranes will not generally transfer any personal data outside the Konecranes Group. Konecranes may, however, share your personal data with the affiliates belong to the Konecranes Group or authorized third parties who process personal data for Konecranes for the purposes described in this Policy.

Due to the technical requirements of the processing, some personal data may be located on servers maintained by subcontractors, which have agreed to the data processing standards of Konecranes.

Konecranes may provide aggregate statistics about its customers, sales, traffic patterns, and other related Site information to reputable third parties, but these statistics will not include personal data.

###  Cookie Policy

This Cookie policy informs you how Konecranes uses cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies (jointly referred to as “cookies”) on its website and how you can manage and control the use of cookies on your computer or device.

###  Our use of cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies

###  Cookies

Cookies are small files, typically, of letters and numbers that we put on your computer or device by a web server when you access our website. Cookies are stored on your computer when you access our website.

These cookies are essential for providing you with a seamless experience when you browse our website and also for allowing us to improve our site.

If you continue to use this website with browser settings that enable cookies to be placed on your computer or device we will consider continued visiting and browsing our website as your acceptance of our use of cookies as described in this Cookie policy.

###  Konecranes website may use cookies for various purposes, and in particular to:

• give you a better online experience  
• allow you to set personal preferences  
• protect your security  
• measure and improve our service  
• work with partners and measure marketing  
• allow third party cookies

###  Basic Functions

These cookies are essential for running our website and are one of the key factors in providing you a seamless experience.

###  Improvement

Cookies enable us to improve our website by informing us how the site is used. We do analytical profiling e.g. to understand popularity of different parts of the site or to know if a video file was viewed or abandoned half way through. We also follow where web content is accessed from in order to arrange our site for optimal user experience. We count “Likes” and “Tweets” and follow what content was shared or referenced.

###  Personalization

These cookies help to make the content as personalized as possible, for example by showing you targeted banners and useful recommendations.  
In order to estimate the effectiveness of our promotions and advertising campaigns we examine, if our site was accessed for example because of an email campaign or a link in a referral site.

###  Other

Cookies we use may be set by other websites who run content on the page you are viewing. For example “Like” button from Facebook or a “Tweet” button from Twitter contains such third party cookies.

###  How to Control and Block cookies

Different browsers use different ways to disable cookies, but they are usually found under a Tools or Options menu. A help menu can also be useful. In addition to cookie management, browsers usually let you control files similar to cookies, for example Local Shared Objects, e.g. by enabling the browser’s privacy mode.

You may be able to opt out of certain third party managed advertising cookies directly on applicable third party websites. You may also be able to enable cookies in your browser settings but opt out from receiving behaviorally targeted advertising. For more guidance on your opt-out options, please consult the following opt out and consumer choice related pages of the following initiatives developed by companies in the online advertising industry:  
\- Network Advertising Initiative: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>  
\- Your Online Choices: [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)

You may be able to opt-out of certain third party managed advertising cookies through third party cookie management sites, such as Google Analytics, Add this, Optimizely, Clicktale and Adobe Flash.

###  What if I don’t accept cookies?

If you do not wish to accept cookies from our website, then you may either:  
\- Adjust your browser settings to not accept cookies and delete any cookies already placed by this website; or  
\- Delete any cookies already placed on your computer and not to use this website again

Note that disabling cookies may prevent you from using some parts of our website. If you delete your cookies from the browser, you may need to remember to re-install opt-out cookies

###  Changes to this Cookie policy

Konecranes reserves the right to change and modify this Cookie policy from time to time. When posting changes to this Cookie policy we will change the “effective date” at the top of this Cookie policy.

###  Your Rights and Contact Details

The processing of personal data is based on your consent. Therefore, you may at any time exercise your right to revoke your consent by contacting Konecranes. However, please note that by revoking your consent, Konecranes may not be able to provide you information regarding our services and products.

At any time, you may contact Konecranes to check the accuracy of your personal data. Konecranes will, at your request, modify or erase any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated personal data. Please contact the controller of your personal data by sending an e-mail through [webmaster@konecranes.com](mailto:webmaster@konecranes.com).

###  Changes to this Policy

From time to time, Konecranes may change or amend this Policy.  In addition, Konecranes may modify or revoke access to this site at any time with or without notice. It is the recommendation of Konecranes that you revisit this Policy periodically to review any changes to this Policy. Additional questions and comments can be directed to Konecranes via e-mail at [webmaster@konecranes.com](mailto:webmaster@konecranes.com).
